Guide to the Duke University Chapel Recordings, 1954-2002 UA.17.01.0003
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Recordings, 1954-2002; 1
  - "Thanks Mary" - Mary Parkinson Retirement Tribute, Undated; 2359
    - Original betacam-sp videocassette (Box 56, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 BETA-0003)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. Memorial Service, Undated; 2360
    - Tape 1 - Original VHS videocassette (Box 52, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0340)
    - Tape 2 - Original VHS videocassette (Box 52, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0341)
  - Preacher Unknown - "Parable of the Wheat and Tares", Undated; 2362
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0771)
  - Untitled, Undated; 2363
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 58, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1173)
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 58, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1174)
  - Unknown church service and choir performance, Undated
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 56, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0504)
  - William Willimon - "Choice, Chance, or the Hand of God?"; William Willimon - "Thanks, But…"; John Vannorsdahl - "On Hailing Caesar"; William Willimon - "Blessed Are the Poor in Spirit", 1987 September 13; 1987 October 11; 1987 October 18; 1987 November 1
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 56, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0506)
  - Thomas G. Long - "Jesus' Final Exam"; William Willimon - "The Way of Peace"; William Willimon - "The Great Resumption after the Grand Intrusion"; Thomas G. Long - Unknown, 1986 November 09; 1987 December 6; 1987 December 27; 1988 February 28
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 56, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0507)